DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
Jun-seo.
Help me.
I want to learn to love him.
Heo In-gang.
LENA
YOU HAVE TO STAY AWAY FROM HER
SHE'S A COMPLETE PSYCHO
TEN PLANET RYU JI-HYEOK
HEY, CONGRATS ON THE AWARD
I ENJOYED YOUR NEW MOVIE
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
STILL IN THE SHOWBIZ
IS EVERYTHING GOOD?
Why are you here?
I asked you a question.
Didn't you hear me--
What's this?
Get out!
Get your hands off me.
I'm no longer someone
you can lay hands on.
So you've got a pretty face
and a few seconds of fame.
How long do you think you'll last
in a place you don't belong?
Go ahead. Thrash around.
You think you can hide the fact
that you killed your parents?
The one thrashing is you.
It must burn you up
that a nobody like me is thriving.
It makes me laugh
when you do this now.
You little--
Why do you think I came to Jun-seo?
You should have kept quiet
if you didn't want to see me.
What was your plan
going to my boss?
Do I have to spell it out?
To expose your ugly truth.
People deserve to know
that you've got
way too much dirt to be on TV.
I'm going to tell them all.
Your smiles and your tears...
They're all fake.
You act helpless and pitiful
when it benefits you.
And now you're acting
like nothing's wrong.
You think I don't know
you killed both your parents?
You little devil. Die!
Die! Die already!
Die!
- You--
- What are you doing?
Ah-jin.
Jun-seo.
Did you see that?
I'm still stuck in that hell.
Now you get it.
Ah-jin.
Jun-seo...
Let me drive you home.
EPISODE 6: SETTING THE TRAP
Cut. Great work today.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good work.
Good job.
- Good work, guys.
- Thank you, everyone.
- Good work.
- Good job.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
- Great work.
I learned a lot, thanks to you.
Great work today.
Ah-jin.
Do you have a minute?
You know I used to be in an idol band
right?
There was a member, Ji-hyeok
who was more popular than me.
One day at lunch
he ate some macarons
from a fan and got sick.
I was rushed in as a substitute host.
The broadcast folks
noticed me that day
and that's how I ended up here.
But...
I knew from the start
that those macarons contained nuts.
I saw him eating them
but kept my mouth shut.
He left the industry
and does something else now.
But whenever he sees me on TV,
he sends messages to cheer me on.
Every time he does that, I wonder.
"Does he know
that I knew and said nothing?
Is he getting back at me
by texting me
or does he really wish me well?"
Whichever it is,
both are hell for me.
What are you trying to say?
The video at the anniversary party.
I enjoyed it.
Watching you claw your way up
reminds me of my younger self,
so here's some advice.
You're going to do fine without that.
I just don't want you to end up
regretting it like me.
As your senior
I'll always be rooting for you.
NO CALLER ID
DECEMBER 25, SATURDAY
Ms. Baek Ah-jin.
I need you to come here.
How did you get my number?
It wasn't so hard.
Anyway, that's not the point.
We need to finish our talk
from last time.
I've got nothing to say.
Then who should I tell
your secret to?
Ms. Baek.
Are you okay with me
spilling your past
to whomever I want, huh?
Fine, send me the address.
Honestly, I don't get it.
All the other groups still hang out
after they disband.
But look at us.
We always meet separately.
So?
What's your point?
Frankly, you're the one
I don't get most.
Right.
It's not like Ji-hyeok ending up
at the ER was your fault.
And you filling in
as a substitute host?
Dude, that was ages ago.
You done?
You're really not going to see him?
He misses you.
You know that.
Man, this feels good.
Enjoying the view?
What the heck are you doing?
I thought about it
and I figured I should show you
rather than tell you.
Take a good look.
That's your future.
See the kid in the blue hoodie?
Doesn't he look familiar?
When he was a rookie,
his bullying past came out
so his career died instantly.
He was finished.
But people already knew his face.
He was young but had no skills.
Yet he still wanted to party.
So, what happens?
He starts bouncing around clubs,
popping whatever he finds.
Then he ran into me.
You're next, Ah-jin.
Look forward to it.
As much as my life burned down
your life will also
come to an end.
I hoped I was wrong.
But it really was you, Ah-jin.
Does Ms. Seo know?
That you're slipping
in and out of VIP rooms?
I didn't want to be there.
Someone called me there.
So, if someone calls
you go no matter the place?
Why do you phrase it like that?
No, why do you live like that?
If you think it's unfair, tell me.
Who summoned you to that VIP room?
Of course, you won't say.
Get out of my car.
You can go to whoever calls you.
I said, get out.
Well, well.
Jae-oh is finally working with me.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Nothing.
I heard I'd make good money
if I worked for you.
Plus, you're human, too.
There's got to be
something I can learn from you.
What did you say?
I just want to be useful for once.
Anyway, this job.
It's legit, right?
It's not illegal or anything?
You punk. I'm done with that stuff.
We help people who need it
and get paid fair.
And you can find anyone
if you work for me.
Even your girl.
Gosh.
What girl?
You know, the broom.
How do you know about the broom?
That girl with the broom-head hair
you sketched in lockup every day.
I've got eyes, kid.
I don't need to look for her.
I already know where she is.
What good is knowing
if you can't even meet her?
You never know.
Maybe someday I'll meet her.
That's why I'm busting my ass now!
Okay, then.
To hardworking Jae-oh,
it's time for your first gig.
What is it?
A police officer?
You said it wasn't illegal!
He's a substation cop.
The client wants everything.
Dig up every bit of information
real or not.
Jeez.
How do I even find
information on a cop?
- We need more kimchi.
- Coming right up.
Ma'am, do you have an empty table?
You'll have to sit with someone else.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Excuse me.
One radish soup, please.
Sure thing.
Oh, man. I'm so sorry.
- My bad.
- Be careful.
- I'm really sorry.
- Jeez, never mind.
Gosh.
I apologize.
Forget it.
- I'll pay now.
- Okay.
Thank you for coming.
Have a nice day.
TRANSMITTING
TRANSIMITTING, 50 PERCENT
TRANSIMITTING, 75 PERCENT
TRANSIMITTING, 88 PERCENT
TRANSIMITTING, 99 PERCENT
TRANSIMITTING, 100 PERCENT
Your phone.
You took mine, right?
- Yes.
- Here.
They looked exactly the same.
Lieutenant Park Dae-ho?
I'm here.
- Reporter Lim?
- Yes, nice to meet you.
Hi.
Have a seat.
One iced Americano, please.
That will be 4,000 won.
You know who Baek Ah-jin is, right?
I know her very well.
We were really close, she and I.
Right.
I can tell from your tone
that you two were close.
- You think so?
- Yes.
- Who hired you for this?
- What?
Who hired you
for that background check on the cop?
- Hello?
- What's this?
"Nojeong-dong rooftop house murder"?
"Baek Ah-jin"?
Who am I speaking to?
We need to meet up.
Who the heck are you?
Did you forget my voice?
It's Kim Jae-oh.
Explain.
Why did Ah-jin's name come up
with a murder case?
- You know something?
- Sit.
I'll explain.
She didn't exactly kill him.
But it's not like she didn't, either.
It makes you curious, right?
Other reporters found it hilarious.
You have proof, yes?
I'm a police officer.
We're going to crush her
for good, right?
Is this real?
Did she actually kill--
No, definitely not.
Someone else did it,
and he's in prison now.
A cop tried to frame her back then,
got punished
and has held a grudge ever since.
That cop is
Park Dae-ho?
Yes.
So, does that mean
Ah-jin almost got arrested?
What were you doing
while all that happened to her?
There was nothing I could do then.
Don't tell me
you're also suspecting her.
She was cleared without a charge
and there hasn't been
a problem since.
She'll be in trouble
if the press gets wind of this now.
And that cop is nasty.
Who knows what he might try?
I only saw her on TV
so I thought she was doing fine.
Tell me what to do.
I'll help.
How is it going with Lieutenant Park?
I'm still on it.
I have most of his movements
mapped out.
He'll go wild
if you poke him carelessly.
Do it right.
Don't worry. We've got help.
Help?
Open the door.
Open it!
You'll be glad to see him, too.
Took you long enough.
Do you know how long I waited
out here because of you?
I almost froze to death for beer.
Well, you back now, so say hi.
But it's so late. Say hi to who?
It's been a long time, Jae-oh.
You scared me.
I got out last December.
I served four full years.
What do you do now?
Well...
I just take action
when the office gives me an order.
Deliveries, transfers, transport...
All kinds of stuff.
DIRECT SOLUTION
And I do background checks.
And some odd jobs
when there's nothing else.
Hey.
I thought you'd ignore me
now that you're a celebrity.
You're pretty loyal.
Back off.
No.
I want a good look at my friend.
What's wrong with that?
"Friend"?
Since when were you my friend?
You're right.
Boss?
Make time for me sometime.
The boss will buy you dinner.
Are you for real?
Then I'm asking
for a very expensive meal.
Like what?
Trouble pasta.
You mean "truffle," idiot.
That stuff is crazy expensive.
- Name it. It's on me.
- More?
- What else?
- Chuck flap tail?
Chuck flap tail?
Burgers, pizza.
- That's what you want?
- Jjajangmyeon.
- And this.
- What is that?
- You know, they drop it like this.
- What?
Get in.
What's this?
It's for you.
It's a burner phone.
Drive safely, sir!
Hey.
Come to think of it
you didn't want me
to talk to you in school.
Didn't you hate me back then?
I still do.
Then why did you let me see her?
Don't you like Ah-jin?
Does it look like it?
Wow, you're serious.
That pisses me off.
I just want her to live
an ordinary life.
That's why I need you.
Because she's more likely to live
a normal life
through you, rather than me.
What are you talking about?
Make it simple for me to understand.
Didn't you see her smile earlier?
She rarely smiles like that.
How does she usually smile?
Hi everyone, I'm Baek Ah-jin.
Today is my first shoot with Dazy.
Fashionable and trendy style...
He didn't stand out at first.
But he took off after being
a substitute host on a music show.
HEO IN-GANG WINS AT BLUEDRAGON AWARDS
Then he switched to acting,
met Longstar's CEO, Seo Mi-ri
and became a star.
Maybe because
he's been working nonstop
he's dealing with depression,
panic disorder, and maybe alcoholism.
He still feels guilty about that
substitute host gig from years ago.
He must think he's being punished.
Both his parents died
when he was little.
His dad died in a car accident
when he was eight.
A year later,
on his dad's memorial day
his mom took her own life.
He and his younger brother were
raised by their maternal grandmother.
I LOVE YOU, GRANDMA
I MISS YOU
He's still really close to her.
He always goes to his grandma's
on days off.
No matter how tired he is,
he always answers her calls.
Kitty.
Why did you come alone?
It's well-known among his fans.
For In-gang, his grandma is
the only real anchor.
NAME: HONG KYUNG-SUK,
HOME: K APARTMENT, YEONDU-DONG
MY DAUGHTER EUN-A'S FAVORITE FOOD
MY GRANDSONS' FAVORITE FOOD
IN-GANG WILL BE ON TV TONIGHT
AS AN AWARD SHOW HOST, EUN-A
CLAPPING
HAND EXERCISES
HUMAN BEINGS EVENTUALLY
GROW UP IN LONELINESS
VOLUNTEER WORK
VISIT EUNGWAN TEMPLE
ON THE DAY OF THE FULL MOON
THE SPIRIT OF THE LATE LIM SUN-YE
I've never seen anyone
come alone to perform memorial rites.
Maybe she has no family.
I heard she's an actress.
- An up-and-comer, they say.
- Yes.
She's mostly in films,
so we wouldn't know.
I see.
Yesterday's move
must have been rough.
Yes, I haven't even
finished unpacking.
Thanks for finding me the place.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
It's close to the office
and super nice.
Tell me if you need anything else.
I'll bring it as a housewarming gift.
JINSIU RICE CAKE
Hey, Ah-jin.
Goodness.
Wait.
What's all this?
Sorry.
I ordered by text when I was busy
and typed the wrong number.
This is a four-story building.
I'll give these out on the top floor.
Promise me you won't tell Ms. Seo.
I promise. Let's go inside.
HOME: UNIT 401, BUILDING B,
K APARTMENT, YEONDU-DONG
Hello.
I just moved in downstairs
and brought some rice cakes.
Oh, my. Thank you.
What a sweet young lady.
Not at all. I hope you enjoy them.
Did you happen to visit
Eungwan Temple not long ago?
Yes, I did.
What a nice surprise.
We meet again.
Do you live here?
No, a friend of mine just moved in.
Do you have time?
Today's the day my daughter visits
so I cooked way too much.
If it's not a bother,
would you come in for a quick meal?
Yes, Grandma.
I'm on my way now.
Aunt might be late.
Did you cook a feast again?
I told you not to wear yourself out.
What?
Who's at your place?
It's my daughter's memorial today.
She was in such a hurry
to leave this world
that she went before me.
It's the one day in a year she comes
so I made all her favorite dishes
and I overdid it again.
Oh, dear.
Thank you for the food.
Help yourself.
What's wrong?
There's nothing you like?
Ah-jin.
Step outside.
In-gang, what are you doing?
Don't be rude to a guest.
Get up.
In-gang!
What's this?
Is this really
the kind of person you are?
In-gang.
There's been a misunderstanding.
- She and I met by chance--
- By chance?
You're unbelievable.
What did I do wrong?
I don't see why you're so angry.
You seriously don't?
Then explain it.
Why are you in my grandma's house,
and with what intention?
Hyang-i moved in here.
I came to help her
hand out rice cakes
and ended up going inside.
I had no idea
it was your grandma's place.
Do I need to explain more?
So, you didn't know?
All of this was a coincidence?
- You expect me to believe that?
- I'm sorry
but your grandma invited me first.
She said she cooked a lot
for her daughter's memorial
and asked me to join.
How could I say no?
I guess you don't care
about her opinion at all.
I don't want to hear anymore. Go.
Leave.
At least one thing's clear.
You're still haunted.
What?
The advice you gave me last time.
You told me to stop torturing myself.
But you're the one tightening
the noose around your neck.
The one who's overstepping
and tormenting me
is you.
Then what did you mean
when you said that to me?
You exposed your flaws
to give me advice
so I mistook it for something more.
Why would you push me away like that?
I guess...
that's how you've lived
your whole life.
Are you saying I'm the one at fault?
Do you know
what people say about you?
That you'll die soon.
That you look lonely and on edge.
They act concerned behind your back
but no one has the guts to tell you.
But I...
genuinely worry about you.
You look unstable,
so I can't pretend I don't see it.
I didn't ask you to.
Don't show up in front of me again.
I really liked you...
as a person
and respected you as an actor.
I guess I was wrong.
You're nothing but a coward.
Anyway, I'm sorry
for causing a misunderstanding.
That's on me.
I apologize.
Isn't it time you told me your plan?
What are you trying to do
with Heo In-gang?
Jun-seo.
I told you. I'm going to date him.
I thought I've done enough
for two years, but I was wrong.
You know
how anxious I am right now.
And Heo In-gang is
just a step that I need
in my current situation.
A lovely set of steps
that will help me get to the top.
THE SPIRITS OF THE LATE
MS. KIM AND MR. HEO
I told you not to let
just anyone in here.
Why don't you ever listen?
She was my guest.
Even if I'm old
I can still tell
who's approaching me with a purpose.
You made a big mistake today.
Apologize when you see
that young lady again.
You're wrong.
There are so many dangerous people
in this line of work.
You have no idea.
You know what?
Heo In-gang blew up at me today.
He grilled me about whether
I approached his grandma on purpose.
To be honest, it was annoying.
My original plan was
to meet his grandma only.
I lost my temper
and said whatever came to mind
and his face changed.
I wonder
which part of what I said
touched his heart.
Did it make him sad
or surprised?
Grandma, I'm heading out.
Take this with you.
I should have put myself
in your shoes.
I'm sorry.
But you can't go through life
being too calculating
and pushing people away.
Well, you know...
I'm at the end of the road
but you kids have a long way to go.
In the end
you'll have to lean on other people.
Just
listen to your heart and follow it.
I will.
Today was a win.
I'll find out how he reacts
tomorrow or the next day.
I can't wait.
Ah-jin.
Don't worry, Jun-seo.
I'll date him for exactly a year.
That's all I need.
GEUMHWADANG BAKERY CAFÉ
Director Sung suggested
that we meet here, so I said okay.
Are you sure you're fine?
I'm fine. Who cares?
- We'll meet again next time.
- Sure.
Take care.
In-gang.
I booked Geumhwadang like you asked
but I'm not sure about this.
Thanks for your work.
Anyway, I did as you asked.
Even if anything goes wrong,
leave me out of it.
I'll handle whatever comes.
Don't you worry.
This is our new dessert.
Try it.
It took a lot of trial and error
to nail the taste.
It reminded me of our trainee days.
I thought being an idol singer
was the toughest job back then
but once I lived another life
I realized that nothing was easy.
- Are you doing well?
- Of course.
That's why I came to see you.
And I had something to say.
I actually knew it back then.
That the macarons had nuts inside.
And I knew you saw it
and said nothing.
But you know what?
I ate them on purpose
from the first place.
Because I was living in hell.
The music on stage
made it hard to breathe.
I felt like I'd die if I didn't quit.
So, I ate them
knowing they had nuts in them.
So, stop carrying guilt
about stepping in
as a substitute host that day.
Is this some sudden confession?
I knew my messages
would make you suffer.
So, I'm sorry
for sending them anyway.
I'm getting married soon.
I'm more at peace than ever.
Maybe it's time...
you let go.
No, In-gang.
Calm down.
Was her name Baek Ah-jin?
She came to see me.
I don't know how she knew
but she asked about back then.
"Does he know
that I knew and said nothing?
Is he getting back at me
by texting me
or does he really wish me well?"
Whichever it is,
both are hell for me.
So, I told her,
and she asked me for help.
She said you were tormented
and that she wanted my help.
She seemed like a good person.
It also looked
like she really cared for you.
I'm sorry.
In-gang, what's wrong?
I went to the awards and shot a drama
with her because you asked
but I don't want to be involved
with Baek Ah-jin anymore.
You never complained,
whatever the gig was.
But this one bothers you?
Why?
Did she make a mistake?
Somehow, she keeps overstepping.
It makes me uncomfortable.
And I broke up with Lena for good,
so put out the breakup news soon.
Got it.
Thanks.
No need to thank me. That's a given.
Actors Heo In-gang and Lena
have ended
their public relationship
after a year.
Their agency, Longstar Entertainment
said their busy schedules
created distance
and they decided to return
to being colleagues.
Many fans are disappointed
as the two were seen
as a great match.
What are you doing?
Are you even looking into it?
Why is it taking so long?
And stop whining!
Don't you realize
the monthly support I give you
is more than your salary?
Do your job right before I fire you.
Damn it.
That bitch...
Goddamn it!
It's me.
The materials we discussed are ready.
Can we meet where we did last time?
In about an hour.
Okay.
Gosh.
You're that guy from before.
So what?
- Happy to see me?
- Yeah, sure.
How dare you do this
in broad daylight--
You took bribes to bury a case
when you were on the narcotics squad.
My life's already in the gutter!
But it's a different story
with a celebrity.
One word from me, and Baek Ah-jin
will disappear without a--
Your daughter
did drugs in the States.
Try burying that one, too.
PERSONAL DETAILS
PARK DAE-HO
The suspicions about Baek Ah-jin
in the Nojeong-dong murder case
aren't true.
There's no file.
The person you've called
can't be reached--
Shit.
She probably got to him first.
I told you so.
She's not an easy target.
This won't be simple.
That's what amateurs say.
I wire you ten million won
every month
but all you do is
leave a few comments on my articles.
Aren't you taking it a bit too far?
Don't get touchy
about hearing this from your cousin.
It's not a small amount
to let pride get in the way.
Also, don't you dare
whine in front of me again.
Earn
what you're paid.
That reporter
Lieutenant Park was trying to contact
only writes hit pieces on Boss.
Lim Hee-kook?
Yes, that's his name.
He writes nothing but good things
about Lena or something.
It turns out they're related.
I'll talk to Lena.
What?
You know her?
I hear she's been bullying Ah-jin.
What?
Jeez, she's unhinged.
Why keep poking Ah-jin
when she's done nothing?
By the way,
Ah-jin says she'll date him.
Is that true?
That's her next move.
I thought you two were
into each other.
You're pathetic.
If I were you...
You know what?
Forget it.
Man.
Oh, how did you...
I couldn't get you off my mind
after that night.
Take a seat.
I should have come to you first.
I wanted to apologize.
And to see you again.
I'm sorry.
My boy has been hurt before.
I told him not to do that.
Please don't hold it against him.
He lost his parents in his childhood
and I raised him.
Yes, I know.
I understand.
I also lost my parents
when I was little.
Oh, I see.
But can I ask you something?
Of course.
Why did you cry that night?
Because it reminded me
of my late mom.
She used to love spring greens.
MY DAUGHTER EUN-A'S FAVORITE FOOD
SPRING GREENS, FRESH KIMCHI...
Sorry, I can't stop myself.
Please don't worry
about what happened.
Don't worry, Jun-seo.
I'll date him for exactly a year.
Don't go.
Just stay with me.
That's all I need.
Do you know
what people say about you?
That you'll die soon.
That you look lonely and on edge.
I genuinely worry about you.
I didn't ask you to.
I really liked you
as a person
and respected you as an actor.
I guess I was wrong.
You're nothing but a coward.
You'll stay with me, right?
Don't ever leave me again.
I'm sorry about the other day.
How about dinner tonight?
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE OTHER DAY
HOW ABOUT DINNER TONIGHT?
I'll be free around nine o'clock.
How about Pavilion?
No way.
It's Ah-jin.
Gosh.
Kim Jae-oh is a big shot now,
visiting a celebrity's place.
What's with the suit?
Where were you?
My brother's graduation.
Shouldn't you be eating with him
instead of coming here?
I wish I could
but he won't see me.
Well...
I get it, though.
Why?
Because you're a murderer?
Your brother is an idiot.
I would have kept you close.
Am I wrong?
A brother who would do
anything for me.
I'd stick with him for life.
Your brother's a fool.
You're definitely something else.
You really are.
But for the record,
he's smart as hell.
His grades are amazing.
He's nothing like me.
So, why am I here?
What's up?
Jae-oh.
Can I ask you a favor?
Of course, anything for you.
Shit.
Who turns the wheel like that
out of nowhere?
Are you okay?
Call Longstar, and they'll handle it.
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Hold up.
You're a celebrity.
You are. Right, you're Heo...
Heo.
Gosh.
I've never met a celeb in real life.
I thought you'd be crazy handsome.
Not so impressive, though.
Your tire's blown.
Wait, wow.
Jeez, this is bad.
Anyway, it looks
like I'm partly at fault.
Even my phone's cracked.
Let me borrow your phone
to call the insurance.
No, it's fine. I'm late.
Stop.
Where do you think you're going?
You're going to call the police
and say I'm a hit-and-run, right?
I won't.
And I won't charge you
for the repair.
You can just go.
Stall him as long as you can.
Whatever it takes.
Just make sure
he's late to the restaurant.
Come on. Just let me use your phone.
Jeez.
I didn't do it.
I was just holding it,
and you knocked it out.
- Got it?
- Seriously.
What do we do now?
Shoot.
What's gotten into you?
You called me first.
I figured you could use a friend.
You don't strike me
as someone with a big circle.
What's the truth
with you and Ah-jin?
Be honest.
When we were kids
our parents remarried
and we lived together briefly.
She's my younger sister.
"Oh, I see.
She was your sister."
Did you expect me to say that?
Please.
That's not how a man looks
at his little sister.
You got me.
Darn.
So, it's love, huh?
Sir, I'll get off here.
Ma'am, we close at ten o'clock.
Okay.
Isn't that Baek Ah-jin?
Man, her face and body are unreal.
She's the pure and glamorous type.
No wonder guys go crazy.
With a body like that
shouldn't she dress lighter
for the people?
Spend the night with me, girl.
Wait, who are--
In-gang.
You piece of--
Come here. Let go.
Fucking let me go!
Come here.
Hey.
Move, hey!
- Get lost!
- What?
Get out of here!
You two are lunatics.
Jun-seo, are you okay?
Jun-seo, wake up.
Have you been waiting
this whole time?
I couldn't reach you,
and I was worried.
I couldn't just leave.
I'm sorry.
I got into a minor accident
on the way.
My phone fell into a sewage
and I couldn't remember your number.
You should have gone home
if you couldn't reach me.
You waited for me
in this freezing weather?
I didn't want to miss you.
You're here now, so it's fine.
By the way,
why are you dressed so lightly?
Aren't you cold?
Wear a scarf next time.
I know it's stuffy,
but it keeps you warm.
Am I nagging?
Is this too much?
Yoon Jun-seo!
You missed me, didn't you?
Hi, I'm Baek Ah-jin.
I'm Yoon Jun-seo.
Jun-seo, help me.
I'm always on your side.
Help me.
I want to learn to love him.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Ho-young Yun